(upbeat rock music)
♪ Ow ♪
♪ Mm, yeah ♪
♪ I used to think maybe you loved me ♪
♪ Now baby, I'm sure ♪
♪ And I just can't wait 'til the day ♪
♪ When you knock on my door ♪
♪ Now every time I go for the mailbox ♪
♪ Gotta hold myself down ♪
♪ 'Cause I just can't wait ♪
♪ 'Til you write me you're coming around ♪
♪ I'm walking on sunshine ♪
♪ Whoa, oh ♪
♪ ♪ Whoa, oh ♪
♪ I'm walking on sunshine ♪
♪ And don't it feel good ♪
♪ Hey ♪
♪ All right now ♪
♪ And don't it feel good ♪
♪ Hey ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ I used to think maybe you loved me ♪
♪ Now I know that it's true ♪
♪ And I don't want to
spend my whole life ♪
♪ Just a waiting for you ♪
♪ Now I don't want you
back for the weekend ♪
♪ Not back for a day ♪
♪ No, no, no ♪
♪ I said, baby, I just want you back ♪
♪ And I want you to stay ♪
♪ Oh, yeah, now ♪
♪ I'm walking on sunshine ♪
♪ Whoa, oh ♪
♪ Whoa, oh, oh ♪
♪ And don't it feel good ♪
♪ Hey ♪
♪ All right now ♪
♪ And don't it feel good ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Oh, yeah, now ♪
♪ And don't it feel good ♪
(upbeat rock music)
♪ Walking on sunshine ♪
♪ I feel alive, I feel the love ♪
♪ I feel the love that's really real ♪
♪ I'm on sunshine, baby ♪
♪ Oh, oh yeah ♪
♪ I'm on sunshine baby ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ I'm walking on sunshine ♪
♪ Whoa, oh ♪
♪ And don't it feel good ♪
♪ Hey ♪
♪ All right now ♪
♪ And don't it feel good ♪
♪ I'll say it, say it, say it again now ♪
♪ Oh, , now ♪
♪ Don't it feel good ♪
♪ Now don't it, don't it, don't it ♪
♪ Don't it, don't it, don't it feel good ♪
♪ I'll say it, say it, say it again now ♪
♪ And don't it feel good ♪
♪ Now don't it, don't it, don't it ♪
♪ Don't it, don't it, don't it feel good ♪
♪ Tell me, tell me, tell me again, now ♪
♪ And don't it feel good ♪
♪ Oh, yeah, now ♪
♪ Oh, don't it feel good,
don't it feel good now ♪
♪ Now don't it feel good ♪
♪ Oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah ♪
♪ Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Oh, yeah ♪